"lang"
{
	"Language"	"English"
"tokens"
{
"dk_tail_tooltip"	"Dragon Tail has a whopping 2.5s stun at level 1 (the longest guaranteed stun at level 1), perfect for getting first blood. Stun duration increases only slightly with additional levels."
"dk_blood_tooltip"	"Dragon Blood greatly helps with survivability and regen, allowing you to stay in lane easily and tank for the team."

"dk_fire_tooltip"	"Breath Fire does good damage in medium AOE range. Great for taking out fleeing enemies. Especially useful Dragon Knight's relatively slow movement speed and melee range."
"dk_dragon_form_tooltip"	"Dragon Knight's ultimate turns him into a ranged killing machine with increased attack & movement speed.  The level 1 dragon does damage over time to targets, including structures."
"dk_ab"				"After all of your useful skills are maxed, put points in attributes."
"item_qb_tooltip"	"Quelling blade helps you get last hits early game by boosting damage against creeps.  It can also be used to chop down a tree in an emergency (in case Furion traps you or you need to hide in the trees)."
"item_gauntlets_tooltip"	"Gauntlets early on help with Dragon Knight's HP and damage, and can be converted into a bracer later."
"item_branches_tooltip"	"In the early game, branches are the most cost effective way to increase your hero's stats and can be dropped or sold back later when you need the inventory slots."
"item_tango_tooltip"	"Although Dragon Knight has excellent regeneration thanks to Dragon Blood, a set of tangos can help regenerate HP lost to enemy harassment early on and keep you in the action."
"item_boots_tooltip"	"Dragon Knight is one of the slower heroes, so getting boots early helps him chase and escape."
"item_pt_tooltip"		"Power treads provide a better speed bonus than regular boots and also boost Dragon Knight's attributes. Make sure that they are set to Strength mode."
"item_helm_tooltip"		"Helm of the Dominator will allow Dragon Knight to passively gain health on every attack (15% of damage) and take control of a neutral creep for your own nefarious purposes. Later in the game it can be turned into Satanic, which is a very powerful weapon."
"item_bkb_tooltip"		"Black King Bar gives your hero an active ability to become magic immune for a period of time. Make sure to use this ability in team fights, particularly against enemy casters/disablers. It also passively increases the damage and health of Dragon Knight."
}
}