"lang"
{
	"Language"	"English"
"tokens"
{
"sven_support_items"	"Support Items"
"sven_ongoing_items"	"Ongoing Purchases"
"sven_defensive"		"Defensive Items"
"sven_offensive"		"Offensive Items"
"sven_clarity"			"Clarity potions help you to cast Storm Hammer early on when your mana pool is small."
"sven_courier"			"Either you or another support hero on the team (but not both!) should buy a courier. Make sure to use the item from your inventory to bring the courier to life!"
"sven_ward"				"When playing Sven in a support role, make sure to keep buying Observer Wards when available to maintain vision of the map."
"sven_gauntlet"			"A gauntlet early on helps with survivability and damage, and should be turned into a Bracer later."
"sven_bracer"			"A bracer helps Sven with survivability and can later be turned into a Drum of Endurance."
"sven_boots"			"Boots increase Sven's movement speed, which (in combination with Warcry) makes Sven great at chasing down fleeing enemies and stunning them. Make sure to upgrade these into Power Treads later."
"sven_mekansm"			"If your team is having a hard time against area of effect damage, Mekansm will help by restoring 250 HP to all allied heroes in range.  Don't buy this if someone else on the team already has one."
"sven_pipe"				"If your team is facing strong magic damage, Pipe of Insight can be useful as it will place a shield around all allied units to block up to 400 magic damage."
"sven_storm_bolt"		"One of the better stun skills in the game. Very easy to use and, if placed correctly, can stun multiple units."
"sven_great_cleave"		"Does splash damage to nearby units, which is only helpful when your damage gets high enough for this to matter."
"sven_warcry"			"Great early on for chasing/escaping, and the armor bonus makes Sven pretty beefy in the early game."
"sven_gods_strength"	"Makes Sven hit hard for 25 seconds - long enough for most teamfights.  Don't forget to pop this at the start of a big fight."
"sven_stats"			"Normally you'd max out stats in the late game, but consider putting a point here early on if you need a little more mana/tankiness."
}
}